<xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8">
<Device name="Aeotec Recessed Door Sensor 7" version="1.4" url="https://aeotec.freshdesk.com/helpdesk/attachments/6092013991" Manufacturer='0x371' ProductType='0x102' ProductID='0xBB'>
  <Groups>
    <Group ID='0' default='open'>Basic Functionalities</Group>
	<Group ID='30' default='open'>Advanced Functionalities</Group>
	<Group ID='40' default='open'>Reporting Functionalities</Group>
	<Group ID='50' default='open'>Limits</Group>
	<Group ID='80' default='open'>Alarms</Group>
	<Group ID='100' default='open'>Reporting</Group>
	<Group ID='200' default='open'>Calibration</Group>
	<Group ID='240' default='open'>Reset</Group>
</Groups>

<Parameters>

<Parameter name="1" group="100" access="rw" type="radio">
<Setting  values="0,1" default="1" size="1" />
<Title>Binary Sensor Report</Title>
<Description>
This parameter is used to enable/disable the binary sensor report. This allows for backward compatibility to report Binary if Notification Report cannot be used for status changes. (1-Byte)

0 = Disable. Sensor Binary Report will NOT be issued via Lifeline when magnet is away or near.
1 = Enable. Sensor Binary Report will be issued via Lifeline when magnet is away or near. 
</Description>
</Parameter>


<Parameter name="2" group="100" access="rw" type="radio">
<Setting  values="0,1" default="0" size="1" />
<Title>Reverse Sensor Reports</Title>
<Description>
This parameter is used to reverse how the sensor reports. Both the Sensor Binary Report and Notification Report are affected by this setting. (1-Byte)

0 = Open Status when magnet is Away. Close status when magnet is near. This is the default mode of operation.
1 = Closed Status when magnet is Away. Open Status when magnet is near.  
</Description>
</Parameter>


<Parameter name="3" group="100" access="rw" type="radio">
<Setting  values="0,1,2,3,4,5,6" default="1" size="1" />
<Title>Association Group 2 Settings</Title>
<Description>
This parameter is used to configure the Basic Set value. Determines the Basic Set value to control other Z-Wave devices directly when magnet is away or close. (1-Byte)

0 = Disable completely.
1 = Send Basic Set 0xFF when magnet is away, and send Basic Set 0x00 when magnet is close.
2 = Send Basic Set 0x00 when magnet is away, and send Basic Set 0xFF when magnet is close.
3 = Only send Basic Set 0xFF when magnet is away.
4 = Only send Basic Set 0x00 when magnet is close.
5 = Only send Basic Set 0x00 when magnet is away.
6 = Only send Basic Set 0xFF when magnet is close.
</Description>
</Parameter>


<Parameter name="4" group="30" access="rw" type="text">
<Setting from="1" to="1535" default="0" size="2" />
<Title>Application Layer Retry</Title>
<Description>
This parameter is used to configure number of retries and wait time between retries. This device supports a retry mechanism when the application of the device detects a transmission error
when the Basic Set, Sensor Binary Report or Notification Report (Access Control) message is sent out but fails to receive an ACK or a Supervision Report. (2-Byte)

This value is expressed as the hexadecimal value of an unsigned integer. For example, a value of 0x05FF would indicate (0x05..) 5 retries with a wait time of (0x..FF) 25500ms between retries.
This would equate to an integer value of 1535. https://www.rapidtables.com/convert/number/hex-to-decimal.html

Value 1 (0xXX..) = Configure the number of retries in a range of 0-5. A value of 0 disables retries.
Value 2 (0x..XX) = Configure the wait time between retries in a range of 0-255. Unit value is 100ms. 
</Description>
</Parameter>


<Parameter name="5" group="30" access="rw" type="range">
<Setting from="0" to="50" default="15" size="1" />
<Title>Supervision Report Wait Time</Title>
<Description>
This parameter is used to configure the time the device waits to receive a Supervision Report. Note that issuing Basic Set, Sensor Binary Report or Notification Report (Access Control) via
association groups uses Supervision Encapsulation only if sending commands with S2 or higher security encapsulation. This parameter can be configured in any network, but only functions with
S2 or higher security. (1-Byte)
</Description>
</Parameter>


<Parameter name="81" group="0" access="rw" type="radio">
<Setting  values="0,1,2,3" default="3" size="1" />
<Title>LED Indicator</Title>
<Description>
This parameter is used to configure the operation of the LED indicator on the device. (1-Byte)

0 = Completely disable LED.
1 = LED quickly flashes only when sending Basic Set, Sensor Binary Report or Notification Report (Access Control).
2 = LED activates only when sending Wake Up Notification.
3 = LED quickly flashes when sending any notification type.
</Description>
</Parameter>


<Parameter name="90" group="0" access="rw" type="text">
<Setting from="10" to="50" default="30" size="1" />
<Title>Low Battery Threshold</Title>
<Description>
This parameter is used to configure the low battery threshold. A battery report will be issued when the battery level is less than or equal to the threshold setting. Unit is expressed in
%. (1-Byte)
</Description>
</Parameter>


<Parameter name="101" group="100" access="rw" type="text">
<Setting from="1" to="14400" default="70" size="2" />
<Title>Timed Battery Report</Title>
<Description>
This parameter is used to set how often the battery level is reported (in minutes). (2-Byte)
</Description>
</Parameter>


</Parameters>
</Device>


</xml>
